{
  "extraDescription": "for numbers in 76-100",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Express 92 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "92,1,23,4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 83 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "83,0,83,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 93 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "93,0,31,3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 99 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "99,1,11,9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 81 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "81,1,9,9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 79 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "79,0,79,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 88 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "88,1,11,8"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{100}\\)",
      "answer": "10",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 87 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "87,0,29,3"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{81}\\)",
      "answer": "9",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 86 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "86,0,43,2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 96 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "96,1,12,8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 100 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "100,1,10,10"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 89 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "89,0,89,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 97 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "97,0,97,1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 84 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "84,1,12,7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 76 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "76,1,19,4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 90 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "90,1,10,9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 85 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "85,0,17,5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 91 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "91,0,13,7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 77 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "77,0,11,7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 82 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "82,0,41,2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 94 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "94,0,47,2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 80 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "80,1,10,8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 78 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "78,1,13,6"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 95 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "95,0,19,5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express 98 as a product of two whole numbers. If possible, the two whole numbers must be greater than 1.",
      "numberInputTypes": ["fac"],
      "answer": "98,1,14,7"
    }
  ]
}
